lacava.com 2007-05-15

# Lacavadesign.com

**1.888.522.2823 **  

| 

* * *  
  
---  
  
HOME PAGE  
  
* * *  
  
COLLECTIONS  
  
* * *  
  
ONLINE LITERATURE,  
SERVICE PARTS  
DISCONTINUED PRODUCTS  
  
* * *  
  
INQUIRIES  
  
* * *  
  
LACAVA PROFILE  
  
* * *  
  
CONTACT INFO  
  
* * *  
  
TERMS AND CONDITIONS  
  
* * *  
  
LACAVA BUSINESS ETHICS  
  
* * *  

* * *  
  
LACAVA  
BATHROOM DESIGN

LACAVA  
BATHROOM DESIGN

LACAVA  
BATHROOM DESIGN

LACAVA  
BATHROOM DESIGN

** Lacava LLC Privacy Statement  
**Updated: April 22, 2005 

This privacy statement has been created to disclose how the information collected on this web site is used. Lacava LLC recognizes that privacy is an important issue in the information age, thus, our firm is greatly committed to our customers’ privacy. 

**TYPES OF COLLECTED DATA**

When you visit lacava.com, you may willingly provide us with your personal information if you choose so. This information is entered in the Questionnaire area where you can submit all your inquiries and order forms where you can purchase our catalog, parts, etc. The information you provide in your direct emails is also collected for future offline communication with you regarding promotional events, trade shows, newsletters, etc. 

In addition to that, we automatically collect some browser information, which does not contain your personal information. This data includes IP addresses (the Internet address of your computer), web pages visited on our website, browsing time duration of your visit, search engines used, the computer type, operating system, etc. This information is used to improve our web site performance and enhance our Internet presence. 

When you visit our web site, the browser might implant files known as “cookies” on the hard drive of your computer. These are amicable files to help you open pages of our web site faster if you had opened them on your computer before. This enhances the performance of our web site. 

**USE OF COLLECTED DATA**

The data and personal information collected on this web site is used to provide the services you have requested, answer your questions, and implement your suggestions. Lacava LLC may use your personal information to make its customer service more effective, to improve the web site in eliminating your hassle of repeated entering the same information, and to enhance Lacava products and services overall. The data collected from different sources may be combined to create your comprehensive profile and minimize inconsistencies. Lacava LLC may use your personal information to communicate important information, news, and other promotional materials, as well as critical notifications regarding the product you have purchased. Your voluntary disclosure of your personal information to us grants Lacava LLC an automatic permission to provide you with updates on Lacava products, upcoming events, and other promotional materials provided online and offline. The data may be used for anonymous demographic information for research purposes to enable us to produce more relevant content. Should you decide to forfeit such communication, please send your request to [info@lacava.com](mailto:info@lacava.com) with the word “remove” in the subject line. 

The automatically collected data, including your IP address, is used to recognize your shopping cart to make your purchasing experience easier. 

**SHARING COLLECTED DATA WITH OTHERS**

Areas of this web site that serve you to conduct e-commerce may share your information with outside companies to allow for processing of those transactions. 

Occasionally, Lacava LLC hires outside services to perform mailing and other promotional services, in which cases the collected data is shared with those outside companies. However, those companies are only provided the personal data necessary for delivery of the service and are required to keep the information confidential and prohibited from making use of that data for any other purposes. Lacava LLC may be required to disclose personal information in legal proceedings if ordered so by the law, or to protect our company, rights, and property. 

With exception of this narrow provision stated above, Lacava LLC does not share, sell, license or disclose your personal information with any outside parties. 

**SECURITY OF COLLECTED DATA**

Lacava LLC is dedicated to maintaining your personal information secure. Thus, we utilize various security technologies in a physical, electronic, and procedural sense in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosures. The security measures include controlled facilities, and limited electronic access, among other things. All sensitive personal information, foremost online credit card payments, is transmitted in an encrypted format, like HTTPS (Hypertext Transfer Protocol over Secure Socket Layer, or HTTP over SSL). 

Other less sensitive information, including direct email communication, is not encrypted, so you transmit it to us at your own risk. In fact, we highly discourage providing us with your credit card information through email; instead, over the phone or fax authorizations are preferred. 

**UPDATES OF THIS STATEMENT**

We reserve the right to modify, change, or update this privacy statement without notice. All changes will be posted online and effective on the date of being posted. The most current date of the update or modification is stated on this page. We encourage you to review this privacy statement every time you visit lacava.com. Using our web site, you express your consent to use your personal data as described herein. 

**UNSUBSCRIBING**

You can request to be removed from our databases to stop our communication with you at any time. Please write to Lacava LLC, 2243 S. Throop St., Chicago, IL 60608; or email [info@lacava.com](mailto:info@lacava.com) with “remove” in the subject line. Even if your personal information is removed from our promotional databases, all past transactions with you will remain on our records for accounting control and product servicing. 

**COMMUNICATION REGARDING THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Should you feel necessary to communicate your questions or concerns regarding this privacy, please feel free to write to Lacava LLC, 2243 S. Throop St., Chicago, IL 60608. 

We welcome your inquiries and hope to exceed your expectations in every area of our business policies.
